I'm Bart and CEO of navitrans navitrans
is a software development company making
solutions for the logistic and transport
sector well for n is hard to find the
right uh employee with the right
background with the right training and
with the right certification and the the
war of talent is ongoing for many years
so we were also looking for an
alternative that's where the rescale
program came
in the power of the reskilling program
is actually to boost your confidence and
to make sure that you just achieve your
professional goals I really wanted to
work behind the scenes uh analyzing
processes creating new flows and that's
why I uh joined the rescaling program
before this I was a key user in other
Erp system and this was like solving
problems in the it I've always been
focused on systems and and work process
and workflows I have the feeling that uh
business Central will be more and more
important in the next years it feels
like we're in the middle of a oldish
they prepped us really good with the
professional skills they taught us a lot
about uh client communication they made
sure that we were in a very safe
environment where we could share our
thoughts with each other the most
surprising element about the program was
that there are not only functional
skills but also soft skills that we
learn consultant mindset communication
presentation skills uh the res program
took away my fear for change because
this was well structured plan there is a
lot of communication and a lot of good
info we have hired uh 10 people in less
than 3 months seven consultants and
three developers they have their contact
person their coach their trainer and we
have recruited them in four different
countries the benefit of uh the res
skill program is that we have only one
single point of contact for all the
countries that we are active in as in
Belgium the Netherlands Denmark
Lithuania so that's very convenient
another benefit is that they are uh
trained the latest versions of business
Central and they can uh hand over those
tips and tricks as well to other
colleagues after 12 weeks they started
being billable which is a very big
Advantage for us as a company we
experienced the the hiring process with
the res skill program is a very fast
process which give us also the certified
and experienced people that we're
looking for the future is business
Central and in my opinion the time to
switch is now and the res skill program
has been a great help for
[Music]
me